{
	"title": "Letters",
	"total": 9,
	"courses": [
		{
			"id": 1,
			"title": "A-B-C",
			"quizzes": [
				{
					"id": "a",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"A\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["A", "B", "C"],
						"correct": "A"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "b",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"B\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["A", "B", "C"],
						"correct": "B"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "c",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"C\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["A", "B", "C"],
						"correct": "C"
					}
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"id": 2,
			"title": "D-E-F",
			"quizzes": [
				{
					"id": "d",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"D\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["D", "E", "F"],
						"correct": "D"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "e",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"E\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["D", "E", "F"],
						"correct": "E"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "f",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"F\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["D", "E", "F"],
						"correct": "F"
					}
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"id": 3,
			"title": "G-H-I",
			"quizzes": [
				{
					"id": "g",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"G\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["G", "H", "I"],
						"correct": "G"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "h",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"H\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["G", "H", "I"],
						"correct": "H"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "i",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"I\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["G", "H", "I"],
						"correct": "I"
					}
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"id": 4,
			"title": "J-K-L",
			"quizzes": [
				{
					"id": "j",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"J\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["J", "K", "L"],
						"correct": "J"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "k",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"K\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["J", "K", "L"],
						"correct": "K"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "l",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"L\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["J", "K", "L"],
						"correct": "L"
					}
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"id": 5,
			"title": "M-N-O",
			"quizzes": [
				{
					"id": "m",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"M\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["M", "N", "O"],
						"correct": "M"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "n",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"N\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["M", "N", "O"],
						"correct": "N"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "o",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"O\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["M", "N", "O"],
						"correct": "O"
					}
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"id": 6,
			"title": "P-Q-R",
			"quizzes": [
				{
					"id": "p",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"P\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["P", "Q", "R"],
						"correct": "P"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "q",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"Q\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["P", "Q", "R"],
						"correct": "Q"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "r",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"R\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["P", "Q", "R"],
						"correct": "R"
					}
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"id": 7,
			"title": "S-T-U",
			"quizzes": [
				{
					"id": "s",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"S\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["S", "T", "U"],
						"correct": "S"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "t",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"T\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["S", "T", "U"],
						"correct": "T"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "u",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"U\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["S", "T", "U"],
						"correct": "U"
					}
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"id": 8,
			"title": "V-W-X",
			"quizzes": [
				{
					"id": "v",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"V\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["V", "W", "X"],
						"correct": "V"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "w",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"W\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["V", "W", "X"],
						"correct": "W"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "x",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"X\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["V", "W", "X"],
						"correct": "X"
					}
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"id": 9,
			"title": "Y-Z",
			"quizzes": [
				{
					"id": "y",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"Y\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["Y", "Z"],
						"correct": "Y"
					}
				},
				{
					"id": "z",
					"explanation": "This is letter \"Z\"",
					"question": "What letter is that?",
					"answer": {
						"options": ["Y", "Z"],
						"correct": "Z"
					}
				}
			]
		}
	]
}